I'm Kitaura Nozomi.
のぞみ 私北浦希
So, what did you want to talk to me about?
なお (菜緒) それで私に話って?
Is it true...
あなた…
that you're dating Uehara Hisashi?
うえはらひさし 上原久志と 付き合ってるって本当?
Huh?
え?
It's a simple question.
㈱簡単な質問だと思うけど
Just say yes if it's true, or no if it's not.
そうならそう違うなら違う
Which is it?
どっち?
I can hardly see a thing from here.
(まりな) こっからじゃ よく見えないし
Me... and Uehara...
私と上原君は
are dating.
つ...付き合ってます
I see.
そう
Then I just might cause you some trouble.
あなたにはつらい思いを させるかもしれない
You see...
私上原久志のことだけは 絶対に許さない
That diabolical man deprived me of my happiness.
私の幸せを奪った つた 極悪非道なあの男だけは…
Uh-oh! Hey!
(まりな)ああ ちょっとあっ! あっ なと
How are you? Are you okay?
大丈夫? ケガしてない?
Yes, I'm fine.
うん 大丈夫
OK, bye.
(AP) C
Oh my god. I could fall in love with her.
(まりな)ヤバっ 好きになっちやうかも
Nao.
(まりな)菜緒
Marina.
(菜緒) まりな
You OK?
ん?
Hey, you!
(希)待って
You still remember me, don't you?
(希)私のこと覚えてるよね
Who are you?
仩原)誰?
Even from a woman's perspective, that girl is pretty fascinating.
(まりな) まあ女から見ても 魅力的だよねあの子
Oh! I'd better add her to my list.
あつー まりなのリストに加えとこ 応
-You're so unfaithful to me. -Huh?
(光石)節操ないなもはや まりな)ん?
All that stuff about not forgiving him
(阿部)いやでもさ 許せないとか
and having her happiness snatched away...
何か奪ったって つたつ 言ってるってことは
then something must have happened between them.
上原といろいろ あったってことだろ?
Nao, has he ever said anything about her?
よしかわ 吉川そのことについて何か
No, I guess he hasn't.
聞いてるわけないか
Well, you know how Uehara never talks about himself.
(まりな) まあ上原君
Yeah! That's right! He doesn't!
そう!そうなんだよ
Besides, he's not the type to do anything mean to anyone.
上原君誰かにひどいこと するようなタイプじゃないし
It's probably just a simple misunderstanding.
たぶん誤解が誤解を 生んだんじゃないかなって よつ
Really?
ほお!
Well, I am his girlfriend, after all.
まあ彼女ですから
So, I really ought to trust my boyfriend.
彼氏のことはねえ 一応は信じないとなあって よめつ
You've really matured, Nao.
菜緒大人になったな
I want us to be more like you and Mitsuishi.
だってまりなとみつちゃん みたいになりたいんだもん
What do you mean by that?
何?うちらみたいにって
Usually you two argue.
普段は 口ゲンカばっかしてるけど
But, like when you were on the Ferris wheel
観覧車の時みたいに
and the two of you are alone... You know what I mean?
2人っきりになった時は… ねえ?
You saw that?
(まりな)見てたの!?
-Of course I saw. -Really?
(菜緒)そりゃ見てたでしょ (まりな)え?
I saw it too.
見ました
-Ow! -Why were you looking?
(阿部)イッテ (光石)何だお前は 部)
From appearances, you don't seem to get along.
見た感じよく分かんないのに
But actually, you've got a close relationship with each other.
実は深いところで 2人は繋がってましたみたいな
We don't seem to get along? I'm not sure I like the sound of that.
見た感じ分かんないって それどうなの?ねえ
Anyway, you two will become like that in no time.
まあまあ菜緒たちも すぐにそうなるから
I mean, think of all the ordeals you've gone through together.
あんだけ試練かいくぐって きたんだから
Yeah, I guess so.
まあね
I do have to admit that we've become more settled and comfortable as a couple.
ちょっとは動じない 2人にはなったと はな とは
That Kitaura, the transfer student,
(七瀬)北浦さんだっけ
she's got such a great figure and is totally cool.
あの転校生スタイルいいし 超かっこいいんだけど
She and Uehara were arguing, so do you think they used to be a couple?
(敦子)言い合いしてたけどさ 元カノってこと?上原君の
Could be! I mean, they're both so calm and cool.
(七瀬) っぽい!何か 2人ともクールで雰囲気似てるし
Uh, Nao, I don't think you should let that kind of talk get to you.
(まりな)あ~菜緒ああいうのはね あんまり気にしないほうが
It isn't! It doesn't bother me at all! Not in the least!
(菜緒)何が? 全然気にしてない全然…
Oh, let's get studying, everyone!
あっ勉強しようみんな
Come on everyone! Let's study. I love studying!
あつみんな勉強 勉強大好き
Oh, dear! I've just got to study!
ヤバい勉強しないと
-It's upside-down. -She's totally losing it.
逆だよそれ逆 (光石)動 まくってんな じ
Really? You don't know a thing about Kitaura?
(菜緒)ねえ本当に知らないの? 北浦さんのこと
I told you, I don't know her.
(上原)だから知らねえって
Did something happen between you two, but you totally forgot about it?
実は昔いろいろあったけど コロっと忘れちやったとか
No, I guess you're right. Nothing happened.
ないよねそんなこと やっぱ
She just came up to me and declared war.
あいつが勝手に 宣戦布告してきただけ
Declared war?
宣戦布告?
Yeah, like, "I'm going to crush you."
俺を潰すとか言ってた
I can't believe that Kitaura would pick a fight with you.
北浦さん上原君に ケンカ売るなんて
-Jeez, what a pain in the ass. -Huh?
あ~面倒くせ~ (菜緒)え?
I've made up my mind about her.
俺決めたわ
I'm never having anything to do with her again.
あいつとは 二度と関わらねえ
Oh...
そっか…
I see! Good! Good!
何だそっかそっか!
What're you smiling about?
何笑ってんだよ
Oh, uh...
あついや…
I'm not smiling about anything.
ぜ…全然笑ってないし
She's quite a lot of trouble, isn't she? Yes, a lot of trouble.
困ったもんだよね?うん 困った困った
Nao!
いっせい (一星)吉川!
-Oh, Issei. -Glad I ran into you.
(菜緒)あついっちゃん (一星)ちょうどよかった つに
Thanks for going out with me the other day.
これこの前 遊園地付き合ってもらったお礼
-It's roast pork. -What? Really?
(一星)チャーシュー (菜緒)えついいの?
Roast pork?
(上原)チャーシュー
Enjoy it together. See you.
(一星) 2人で仲良く食ってくれや じゃあな
Thank you.
ありがとう
Wow, this is really nice.
(上原)は~いいなこれ
-Let's make fried rice with it. -No, way.
(菜緒)チャーハンにしよう (上原)チャーハンじゃねえ
-We're making pork roast steaks. -No! Fried rice!
(上原)チャーシューステーキだよ (菜緒)チャーハンだよ!
What're you talking about? Pork roast steaks!
(上原)何言って チャーシューステーキだよ
-I say fried rice! -And I say pork roast steaks!
(菜緒)チャーハンだってば! (上原)チャーシューステーキ
OK, back to work. Back to work!
(一星) さあ!仕事仕事
Just slice it up into steaks.
仩原) このまま ステーキにすんだよ
You've never even cut one of these!
(菜緒)上原君なんて 切ったことないでしょ
Yes, I have. We're having pork roast steaks.
(上原)あるよ チャーシューステーキだよ
Just look how good it is!
こんないい チャーシューねえぞ
-I'm telling you, fried rice! -No! Pork roast steaks!
(菜緒)チャーハンだってば こつ (上原)チャーシューステーキだよ
Kitaura and Uehara were at it again today.
(夏海)ねえ今日もやり合ってたね 上原君と北浦さん
Those two should become a couple.
(弥生)もうさあの2人 くっついちゃえばいいのに
-Yeah! They're a perfect match. -Oh, no!
(夏海)確かにめっちゃお似合い (菜緒)あれ?
Yeah!
(BME)
Uehara and Kitaura are such a great match.
(桜)上原君と北浦さんって お似合いだよね
I totally see it! It's like he lets her do that to him.
(聖奈)分かる北浦さんだったら 許すって感じしない?
-Oh, totally! -I told you!
(桜)あつ分かる 俚奈)分かる?
Oh, dear!
あれれ?
What is it?
何?
Oh... uh... well...
あっえっいや つえつ
I was just wondering how you and that Kitaura are getting along lately.
例の北浦さんとは 最近どうかなあ?なんて
Oh... I was just kidding.
あ…な~んてね
Sorry! Sorry about that.
ごめんなさい すいません
Good night.
おやすみ
Oh! That's right.
あつそうだ
Tomorrow's Saturday. I'm off work. What about you?
明日の土曜お休みなんだけど 上原君は?
I'm working.
(上 )バイト 原
Figures...
(菜緒)だよねえ
Oh, of course.
そうだよね
He and Kitaura are enemies, after all.
北浦さんとは 険悪なんだもんね
It's all right, I think.
大丈夫だよね
Not even!
HUI
You're so naive, Nao!
甘すぎるよ菜緒は
You have no idea what love can do!
恋心が全くちっとも 分かってない
As usual, you sure are frank about your thoughts, Marina.
相変わらずズバズバ言うよね まりなは
Love that has it's seeds in hate is the kind that becomes the strongest.
嫌いから始まる恋のほうが
Just like someone you and I both know.
誰かさんみたいに
Huh?
(菜緒)え?
Oh, yeah. Uehara. You said you wanted a computer, right?
(明)あっそういや上原君
Yes.
はい
This new customer here says she's getting rid of her old one--
最近うちに通い始めた お客さんでね
Please introduce me to her!
ぜひ紹介してください!
Oh, sure. She always comes when you're not here, so I'll get her--
おお...おお あっ君がさ おさ おが
-Welcome! -Welco...
いらっしゃいませ! (上原)いらっしやいま
What perfect timing!
グッドタイミング!
We were just talking about you, Kitaura.
ちょうど希ちゃんの話 してたんだよ
You mean...
まさか…
Try to remember.
(まりな) よーく思い出してみ?
You yourself, Nao, what did you think of Uehara at first?
菜緒だってさ
He was stuck up... and cruel, and ticked me off.
偉そうだし 意地悪でムカつく
And what do you think now?
それがどうなった?
I think he's super nice and kind.
すっごく優しいんだってなって
I'm... in love with him.
好きだなって
See!
ほら
Oh, no!
あ… め
Attraction is way greater
(まりな) 最初から優しい男より
when you go from hating a guy to seeing how great he is
大嫌いなあのヤローに こんな一面が!?
than when he's a nice guy from the start.
ってほうが クラっといっちゃうんだって
You mean, that's likely to happen between Uehara and Kitaura?
(菜緒)それって 上原君と北浦さんは
From my perspective, it's totally going to happen between them.
大いに当てはまると 私は見てるね
She's the one with the computer--
(明)ほら前にパソコン 処分
-Forget it! -That was fast!
(BB) Rp25
I'm never going to let this guy have it.
(希) こいつにあげるとかは ありえないです
-Sorry. -Oh, I see.
すいません (明)ああ…そう
You're just going to throw it away, right?
どうせ処分すんだろ?
Then give it to me. I'll buy it!
だったらくれ いや買う!
It's a Pro Graphics High Spec Processor model.
ブログラフィックス PRO GRAPHICSの HIGH SPEC PROCESSモデルだけど ハイスペックプロセス
-What would an amateur do with-- -Are you kidding me?
素人には使いこなせない… 仩夙まさか!
Is that the rumored limited edition model?
あの幻の限定モデルか!?
Yeah... it is.
ま…まあ
Oh, god! No!
(菜緒)マズい マズすぎるそれ
And they seem so much alike.
しかも似た者同士な 気もするし
What if they both have the same interests and suddenly hit it off?
何か妙に趣味とか合って 口つ 意気投合しちゃったら
If they hit it off?
し…しちゃつたら?
It'll be too late.
手遅れだね
-Oh, no. -Nao!
(菜緒)え… (まりな)菜緒!
I used to absolutely hate your guts.
俺お前のこと 心底大嫌いだったのに
But now...
Sla...
Me too. I wanted to crush you.
(希)私もお前のこと ぶっ潰すと思ってたのに ふつ漬
Who's that?
あの人は誰?
She's the person who does all the housework around here.
ああ彼女は家事全般を やってくれる人だよ る人に
You're amazing, Kitaura. I learned a lot.
すげえよ北浦 勉強になる
I'm nothing special at all.
べ…別にすごくはない
So, if you play a game with SXGA running
じゃあSXGAで ゲームを走らすと
-it reduces performance? -That's right!
パフォーマンスが下がるってことか そうなんだよ!
That's what I couldn't under...
そこは私も納得がいかな
Huh?
(EPT)
What are they doing together?
(菜緒)何で一緒にいるの?
And it looks like they're hitting it off!
っていうか すでに意気投合してる?
Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
どうしよどうしよ
I think the CXKP...
(上原)俺CXKPって
What are you doing there?
何やってんだお前
What a coincidence.
偶然ですね
Yes, a real coincidence.
偶然だな
The stuff he does is real hit or miss.
(上原) まああの監督 当たり外れ大きいからな
Yeah, you're right.
(希)確かに
But when he works with Woodman--
でもウッドマンと組んだ時は
-It works! -It sure does!
仩原)当たり (希)だよな!
The power and pace are totally different.
勢いっていうか スピードが違う
Yeah, that's so true. Isn't it?
(菜緒)確かにね~ そうだね
Are you going to see him this summer?
(上原)次夏にやるだろ 北浦も見に行くのか?
Of course. You are too, aren't you?
(希)もちろん 上原も行くだろ?
Yeah.
(上原)ああ
There's quite a lineup this summer.
夏はなラインナップが いろいろある
I want to see that match too.
(菜緒)あっ私も見た こいな その試合
-It's a movie. -Huh?
(上原)映画だぞ (菜緒)え?
A movie.
(上原)映画
Oh, I was confused, I guess.
(菜緒)あつ勘違いしちゃつた
If it's that amazing,
そんなに面白いなら
then I'd like to see it with you.
私も今度 連れてってほしいなあ
Movies are meant to be watched alone.
映画は1人で見るもんだろ
-You can't focus with someone next to you. -Totally.
誰か隣にいると気が散るしな (上原)だよな!
It's especially impossible if it's someone you know.
知ってる奴が隣とか 本当無理だわ
And those people who eat popcorn all through the movie.
あと上映中 ポップコーン食べ続ける奴
Yeah! It's like, why'd they come to the movie if they're going to do that?
いるよなそういう 何しに来たか分かんない奴
And there're the type that always spills stuff too.
ああいう奴に限ってさ こぼすんだよな
-Oh, no! -What's wrong with you?
(菜緒)あっ! (一星)お前何やってんだよ
Fighting with your boyfriend again?
また彼氏に 何か言われたか?
-Can I ask you something, Issei? -Yeah.
いっちゃんさ (一星)おう さう ち星
Do you know the names of foreign movie directors?
外国の映画監督の名前とか 知ってる?
No idea.
(一星)知らん
Do you eat popcorn in the movie theater?
じゃあ映画館で ポップコーン食べない?
Of course I do!
食べるに決まってんだろ!
Popcorn and a giant soda are essential!
ポップコーンとコーラのLは 必需品だろ?
I couldn't agree more!
だよね!
I didn't realize Issei and I had so much in common.
って…いっちゃんとは こんなに合うのに
Huh?
あれ?
Aren't you working today?
上原君今日 バイトじゃないの?
I'm off. What about you?
(上原)休み お前は?
-I'm working. -Oh. See you later.
(菜緒)バイト... (上原)ふーんいってらっしゃい 小
We only see each other in passing.
すれ違ってばっか
Uhm, can I ask you about Kitaura?
あのさ上原君 北浦さんのことなんだけど
Yeah?
(EIA)
You two came to terms, didn't you?
(菜緒)仲直りしたんだね
Yeah, I guess so.
ああまあ めめまめ
It's not like we were fighting anyway.
てか別にケンカしてた わけじゃないしな
She's a pretty nice person.
あいつ結構いい奴だし
I see.
そっか…
Well, that's good.
それはよかった
OK, see you later.
じゃあいってきます
You'll get run over if you keep looking down like that.
(一星)下ばっか見てると 車ひかれっぞ
Oh, Issei. Good morning.
(菜緒)あついっちゃん おはよう
Morning.
おう
I don't share any of the same interests at all with Uehara.
(菜緒)上原君ときれいさっぱり 趣味合わないんだよね
Yeah, you're right.
(一星)だろうな ろつな
You sure are frank, aren't you, Issei?
(菜緒)結構はっきり言うんだね いっちゃんも
There's no point in lying about it.
(一星)ウソついても 仕方ねえだろ
Jeez... I guess I'm going to have to study up on movie directors and stuff.
(菜緒)はあ... 映画監督とかの勉強しなきゃ
But I get sleepy when I watch complex movies.
でも難しい映画って 眠くなっちやうんだよね
And the stuff Uehara's into is niche.
それに上原君の趣味 マニアックすぎ
What's the big problem with that?
そんなの 大した問題じゃねーって
-Huh? -You know the saying.
(菜緒)え? (一星)ずつと一緒にいると
"If you're always together, you grow more and more alike."
イヤでもよく 似てくるって言うだろ?
It happens to lovers and married couples.
恋人しかり夫婦しかり
Married couples?
夫婦!?
Don't overreact to some particular words.
そこに反応すんなよ
Well, anyway...
まあいいや
When you're with someone for a long time
とにかく!長い間 ずつと一緒にいると
will all become more and more alike.
いろいろ似てくんだよ
Don't let what's happening right now bother you so much.
だから目先のことに あんま振り回されんな
You've already got what's most important.
吉川は一番大切なもの 持ってんだから
I do?
え?
You're more honest and faithful to him than anyone else.
あいつに対して誰よりも まっすぐで誠実なところ
Yeah.
うん
If you've got that, you don't need anything else.
そこさえありゃ あとは何もいらねーって
Just be who you are, Nao.
吉川は吉川らしくしてりや いいんだよ
Thank you, Issei.
ありがとういっちゃん
Besides, fate smiles on those that work hard, right?
まあ頑張ってる奴には
And even when things aren't working out
それでもうまくいかない時は
well... you know...
まあ…あれだ
you can come talk to me. I'll listen to your troubles...
グチなら聞いてやるから いつでも俺んとこ…
She's not even listening to me.
って聞いてねーのかよ
OK.
(菜緒) よいしょ
Oh, sorry about that, Issei.
あつごめんいっちゃん
Huh? What is it?
ん?何?
That's another thing that makes you unique.
(一星) まあそういうとこも 吉川らしいな
Thank you.
(店員) ありがとうございました
Thanks for waiting for me.
悪いな付き合わせちゃつて
No big deal. I was free anyway.
別に 暇だし
Oh, about your computer...
あつパソコンのこと なんだけど
I haven't given you my OK on that!
(希)そこはウンと言ってない
-Forget about it, anyway. -What?
あれもういいや (希)え?
I think it's something that I should buy myself.
何か自分で買うべきもんな 気もするしな
-Don't you ever wonder about it? -About what?
(希)聞かないのか? 仩 )何を? 原
-About why I'm fighting with you. -Oh, that.
(希)私がケンカ売ってる理由 (上原)ああ~
-You've completely forgotten, haven't you? -Yeah.
完全に忘れてただろ 仩原) うん
You're a nicer guy than I thought you were.
上原って思ってたより いい奴だな こな
I never thought you'd be interested in this kind of thing.
(希)上原がこういうのに 興味があるって意外だな
I want fifth prize.
5等当てる
Fifth prize?
5等?
I know somebody who loves that stuff like crazy.
あれバカみたいに好きな奴 いるから
Nao!
(徹平)菜緒ちゃん
Yes?
はーい
Here.
(徹平)はいこれ
Huh? What's this?
えっ何ですか?
I won it at the lottery.
福引きで当たったんだけどな こつにんに
But I can't close the shop to go.
俺店休むわけ いかねえしな
"Ikaho hot spring"?
いかほ (菜緒)伊香保温泉?
Think of it as my way of saying thanks for the hard work you do every day.
(徹平)菜緒ちゃんいつも 頑張ってくれてるから
What? Really? I can have this?
(菜緒)え?いいんですか?
Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます!
Fate is finally smiling on me!
とうとう神様が 私に味方してくれたみたい
You win first prize!
(福引き係) 1等大当たり~!
Congratulations.
(ミス伊香保) おめでとうございます
"A pair of tickets for Ikaho hot spring."
(希)伊香保温泉?ペアか
You should go with your girlfriend.
彼女と行ってくれば いいんじゃないか?
You can have it.
やる
-What? -Take it before I change my mind.
(希)は? (上原)俺の気が変わる前に
Here.
ほら
See you later.
じゃあな
You win the milk pudding! Congratulations!
(福引き係)はい牛乳プリン おめでとう!
Ta-da!
(菜緒)ジャ~ン!
Yeah, way more than you can imagine.
まあ…お前が思ってる以上に びっくりしてるよ
Let's go during the next three-day weekend.
でしよ 今度の連休行こうよ
With whom?
誰と?
What do you mean "whom"? There's only you.
誰って 上原君しかいないじゃん
-Just the two of us? -Uh-huh.
2人で? (菜緒) うん
Oh... I see.
ああ…そう
I'm looking forward to it.
(菜緒)楽しみだな~
This really must be my reward for my hard work every day.
やっぱ日頃の行いの 成果だよね
Don't forget to get the day off from your work.
あっちゃんとバイト 休み取っておいてよ
Yeah.
(上 )おお 原
OK, I'm going to bed.
じゃ俺寝るわ
Don't get yourself injured before we go on this trip.
(菜緒)旅行行く前に ケガしないでよ
Give me a break.
上原) うるせ
Oh, this looks nice.
(菜緒)あついいかも
She has no idea what she's saying. I'm sure of it.
あいつ絶対 意味分かってねーよな
I'm going to bed.
寝よ
I feel stupid worrying over it.
俺だけ悩むのアホくさ
Oh! This place looks nice.
(菜緒)あつここいいな
Oh! Konnyaku balls.
あっ玉こんにゃく
What's that? Are you going on a trip?
(まりな)あれ?旅行行くの?
Uh-huh. With Uehara.
(菜緒) うん!上原君と つん!
Really?
へぇ~ え
Don't tell me you're staying overnight.
まさかのお泊まりとか?
Uh-huh.
うん
What?
え?
Oh, Look at this. These konnyaku balls look delicious.
あつねえねえ
You've got to be kidding me! You never told me about that, Nao!
ウソでしょ? 待って菜緒聞いてないよ
What? What? Ow! That hurts! What's wrong all of a sudden?
(菜緒)何何? 痛い痛いよ何急に?
Why didn't you tell me that you two had that kind of relationship?
もうそういう仲なら そういう仲って言ってよ!
I feel so stupid that I avoided the subject all this time.
何か今まで気回してたの バカみたいじゃん
What's wrong with you?
(菜緒)何何?急に
What kind of relationship are you talking about?
何? ういう仲って そ
-What? Are you serious? -Yes.
え?本当に んってんの? (菜緒) うん
OK, that's it! Get over here!
もう分かる? あーもう来て
-Right now! -Jeez!
早く菜緒 (菜緒)何?
What?
ええ~っ!
What do you mean "what"? That's what I want to say!
"ええ~っ! "って こっちが"ええ~"だからね 44-
Wait! Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ちょっと…ちょっと待って 待って待って
But, we aren't like that at all!
だって…私たちはまだ こつ 全然そういうの
What's going on? What's up with you?
(光石)何何...?何の話?
What did you do this time, Nao?
(阿部) また吉川やらかしたの?
-It's nothing!
(まりな.菜緒)何でもない!
Of course that's what it seems like.
(まりな)絶対そういう感じに なるでしよ
I mean, you're staying overnight, right?
だってお泊まりだよ?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
(菜緒)そうだよね
I was so excited about taking a trip with him...
いや旅行が楽しみすぎて 浮かれちゃつてて
That you didn't think about that.
そこまで考えてなかった
How poor Uehara is!
ふびんすぎるな上原君
What should I do?
(菜緒)どうしよう
There's nothing you can do.
(まりな) えっどうするも何も
You may as well get on with it now that you've come this far.
ここまできたら 覚悟決めるしかないんじゃない?
What? Oh, no! No way!
えっ!いや!ハッ! え~ ええ
Jeez! That's disgusting! And cold!
仩原) うわっ 京)つわつ きったねえ冷てつ
Oh! I'm sorry!
(菜緒)あっ わ…悪かったわね!
What's wrong with you?
(上原)何してんだよ
Ouch!
(菜緒)わつ痛
You're the one who won't be able to go on the trip.
(上原)お前が旅行 行けなくなんじゃないの?
I'm just fine!
(菜緒)大丈夫だから
Ow!
(EEA) TT y
Oh, dear!
(菜緒)どうしよ
Oh, dear! Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
どうしよどうしよ どうしよ
Oh! I know!
ハッ!そうだ
That's it!
そうだよね
That's what I'll do!
うんそうしよう! フフフ
Yea!
ワーオ!
Uehara!
(光石)上原!
What are you going to wear tomorrow? It's still cold up in the mountains.
明日何着ていく? 山のほうまだ寒いよな
What?
(EPT)
It's my first time to go to a hot spring resort.
俺さ温泉旅館って 初めてなんだよね
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみ
Well, Nao, she, uh...
(まりな)何か菜緒がさ
she said that it would be more fun if we all went together.
みんなで一緒に行ったほうが 楽しいって誘われちゃつて
Really?
へえー
Please! Come with us, Marina!
お願い! まりな一緒に行こう
It says up to six people is OK. Invite Mitsuishi too!
6名様までオーケーなんだよ みつちゃんも誘ってさ!
But it would be unfair to Uehara.
(まりな) うーん でも上原君に悪いし
You and Mitsuishi can go to a hot spring resort for free!
みつちゃんとタダで 温泉旅行ができるんだよ!
Huh?
えつあれ?
Well, you know, when we get there,
あつまあほら あっち着いたら
we'll split up and go around just as couples.
彼氏彼女同士で回ればいいし ねえ?
-Yeah, that's right. -Yeah!
(光石)ああうんうん… まりな)ねえ...
-That's what we'll do! -Oh!
(光石)そうそうそう. (阿部)あっ!
There you all are!
みんな集まってんじゃん
Let's decide who's in charge of what on the trip. I'll take care of snacks.
旅行中の担当決めようぜ 俺お菓子担当!
-You're going too? -Naturally!
(上原)お前も行くのな (阿部)もち!
-I'd like to punch your lights out. -Huh?
殴りて~ (阿部)え?
Never mind.
(上原)何でもねーよ
I'm...
ただいま
home.
帰りました
There's something you need to tell me, isn't there?
(上原)お前俺に 言うことあるよな
Oh...
あつ
You mean, about tomorrow?
もしかして明日の…
Since when did this become a group tour?
いつから 団体旅行になったんだよ
Well, you see...
(菜緒)いやその
The voucher...
旅行券ね
Issei's dad gave it to me.
いっちゃんのお父さんから もらったの
It said that it was good for up to six people.
6名様まで オーケーって書いてあって
What?
は?
Don't tell me the ramen shop owner is coming too.
まさかラーメン屋のオヤジまで 来んのか?
No, he has to run the shop.
ううん お店あるし
So Issei is coming instead.
代わりにいっちゃんが 来ることになりまして
Sorry.
ごめんね
I was going to tell you.
ちゃんと話そうって 思ってたんだけど
-Forget it. -Huh?
もういい (菜緒)え?
I'm not going tomorrow.
俺明日行かねーから
What? Wait a second! Why?
えっちよっちよつ… えつ 何でよ?
I hate being in a big group on a trip.
(上原)わいわい旅行とか 面倒くせーし
Invite someone else.
他の奴誘えば?
You can't be serious.
そんな
Hello?
(上原)あつはい
Tomorrow?
(上原)明日っすか?
Yeah, I guess so.
いいつすけど
OK. I'll be there. Good bye.
はい分かりました お疲れさまです
What? Where are you going tomorrow?
何?明日どこ行くの?
I've got work at the gas station.
スタンドのバイト
Another guy can't come in, so they asked me to work instead.
来れなくなった人がいるから 出てくれって
You're so horrible.
UELI...
How can you suddenly cancel like that--
急に行けなくなるとか そんなのひどいよ!
You've got no right to say that!
(上原)どっちがだよ!
If you didn't want to be alone with me, then you should have just told me.
2人きりがイヤならイヤって 最初から言えばいいだろ こう
It's not like I didn't want to.
別にイヤとか そういうのじゃなくて
It's just that the two of us alone...
ただ2人は
I mean...
その...
You see...
だから…
Then just tell me that.
(上原) じゃあそう言えよ
But to decide it all on your own, and go around changing it...
(上原)勝手に決めて 勝手に1人で突っ走って
That means you're only thinking about yourself.
自分のことしか 考えてねーだろお前
Uhm, Uehara.
(菜緒)あのさ上原君
Sorry, but I've got to get to work.
(上原)悪い 俺バイトあるから
-Where's Issei? -He went to look for them.
(光石)-星さんは? (まりな)今見に行ってるでしょ
They aren't upstairs.
(一星)あいつ上にもいねえぞ
What are those two doing? They're so late.
遅いなあ菜緒と上原君 何やってんだろ
-Maybe because it's cloudy. -What's that got to do with it?
(光石)曇りだからですかね まりな)関係ある?
-It does, a little. -You think so?
(光石)多少 まりな)そういうこと?
-Maybe not. -They're not that kind.
(光石)ないかな (まりな) "よう"じゃないから
Nao!
(阿部)吉川!
-Huh? -There she is!
(まりな)え? 侊石)おう
What are you doing over there, Nao?
何だよ菜緒 びっくりさせんなよ
Huh? Where's Uehara?
(阿部)あれ? 上原どうしたんだ?
Oh, dear.
まさか…
Well, I can pretty much figure out what happened between you.
まあ何があったかは 大体想像つくけど.
But what's happened has happened.
でもほら なっちゃつたもんは仕方ない! なつ
That's right! That's right!
そうだそうだあの
Uehara's never going to come if you just sit there.
くよくよしてても 上原来るわけじゃないし
Yeah, you're right.
to NIN...
Cheer up, and let's go!
(まりな)元気出して行くよ!
Ikaho! Ikaho! Ikaho!
伊香保伊香保伊香保 木...
-This way? -No, that way!
まりな) こっちだっけ? (光石)あっちだよ
That way? Really?
(まりな)あっち?本当に?
Must be rough having a fight when they live together.
一緒に住んでてケンカって 相当気まずいよな
What? Nao and her boyfriend live together?
え?吉川と彼氏って
Huh? You didn't know about that?
あれ?一星さん 知りませんでしたっけ?
No.
おう
Mitsuishi! Mitsuishi! Here!
まりな)みつちゃんみつちゃん ほい!
-You want one, Nao? -No, I'm OK.
(阿部)吉川食べる? (菜緒) ううん大丈夫
Can't she even clean up after herself?
ちゃんと片付けろよな
-You want one, Issei? -Yeah.
(阿部)-星さん食べます? (一星)おう -お 部)
-Wow! It's so beautiful! -Wow!
わあー超きれい (阿部)おお
Dang, it's cold!
あー寒い
Oh! Hey, Nao! Let me see that travel guide.
(まりな)あっねえ菜緒 雑誌見せて
OK.
(菜緒)あつ
I wasn't thinking when I left home.
(菜緒)ボーッとしてて家かも 小
What? Are you serious? Oh, no!
(まりな)ええ?マジで? え~
Marina! There's an information booth.
(光石) まりなまりな インフォメーション り!
Oh! An information booth!
(まりな) あ-インフォメーション
-Oh, Abe! -Huh?
(まりな)あっあべっち べつ (阿部)ん?
You want my konnyaku balls?
(女性)タマエの玉こんにゃく 食べる?
Yeah!
(男性)食べる
It's delicious!
(女性)フフッおいしい
Uehara?
(希)上原?
Are you going somewhere too?
お前もどっか行くのか?
Uh, yeah. What about you?
仩原)あつまあ. 北浦は?
Yeah. With that prize you gave me. I thought I'd go have a good time.
(希)あつお前にもらった券で つに 旅行満喫させてもらうことにした
Oh... That...
ああーそう
I'll take a photo for you.
(観光客) じゃ撮りますよ や撮
OK! Ikaho!
(まりな)はい伊香保
OK. Got it.
(観光客)はいオーケーです 撮れました
-How do I see it? -Is the picture good?
(光石)どうやって見んの? どうやって見んの?
Nao.
(まりな)菜緒
-How do you see it? -Don't you know?
(阿部)どうやんの? (光石)使い方
I'm her servant.
(光石)お付きの者
OK, got it.
(菜緒)はいオーケ
That hurts my knees.
(光石) ヒザが痛いんです
-You're next, Nao. -Me?
まりな)はい次は菜緒 (菜緒)え? は?
-I don't need one. -Get over there!
(菜緒)いいよいいよ (まりな)早く
-Smile!
(まりな·光石) ノ17~
OK.
パア~ K7~
Come on, smile! Here we go!
(まりな)笑って はいいくよ
Thank you!
まりな)ありがとう
Hey! Wait for me!
あっ待って待って
OK.
(菜緒) うん
Sorry. I recommended this place, but if you don't like it...
悪いここ俺のイチ押しなんだけど お前の口には
No! It's delicious! Really, it is!
あつおいしいよ おいしい
Oh, I forgot to add pepper.
あっコショウ入れるの 忘れてた
It needs pepper.
ねつコショウ
Hey! Stop! That's too much!
おいおいおい… 入れすぎだろ
It won't taste any good.
味変わるだろ もういいよ
Nao's forcing herself to have a good time.
菜緒絶対無理してるよね
She's totally missing Uehara.
(光石)完全に 上原ロスってやつだな
Oh, well. I guess I'd better help her out.
仕方ない 俺が一肌脱ぐか
I'll send this to Uehara.
これを上原に送る
Uehara couldn't resist this.
さすがの上原も
It'll break his heart to see Nao looking like this.
吉川のこんな顔見たら 心痛むでしょ!
-She's smiling, but... -Her eyes are crying.
(まりな)一応笑ってはいるけど 心夭つ (光石) 目が死んでる
Wait a minute. You know Uehara's number?
てかお前 上原の番号知ってんの?
Of course! We're best friends.
当たり前だろ! 親友だもん
-Go for it, Abe! -Got it!
おーあべっちゴー! (阿部)よっしゃ!
But Uehara never replies very fast.
まあ上原のことだから
Don't expect an answer soon.
そんなに早く 返信来ないと思うけど
I'm still eating.
食べてんだからよ
Don't force yourself to eat it, Nao.
吉川お前 あんま無理すんなよ
No, I'm not forcing myself.
別に全然無理してないよ
Like they say, powerful food is good for the heart and--
刺激強いほうが心身共に スッキリする
Nao!
(まりな)菜緒!
What is it?
(菜緒)何?
Uehara is on his way here!
上原君今向かってるって
He is?
上原君が?
Yep.
うん
I... I'll go and wait for him!
私...私 ちょっと迎えに行ってくる
Oh! Whoa! OK. Sorry. Let me get out of the way.
まりな)あーおうおう よいしょ はいごめんごめん
-Be careful. -OK.
(まりな)気をつけてね (菜緒) うん
That's the best smile she's had all day.
今日イチの笑顔が出たね
It's so easy to tell what she's thinking.
(光石)分かりやす
What time will Uehara get here?
っていうか上原君 何時に着くの?
-Uh... -I don't know.
(まりな)あつ (阿部) さあ
Really?
(光石)え? じゃあ菜緒待ちぼうけかよ
Nothing wrong with that.
いいんじゃないの?
It's pretty fun waiting for someone you love.
好きな人を待つのって 結構幸せな時間だから
You say some pretty great things sometimes.
(光石) たまにいいこと言うんだよな
Hey, Nao.
おい吉川
Oh! Uehara!
あっ上原君
You've been waiting a while, haven't you? You must be cold.
おい待っただろ 寒かっただろ つに
Here. Put on my coat.
俺の上着でも着てろ
No, it's all right, Uehara.
いやいいよ上原君
No, I want you to wear it.
いやいいよ着ろって
Thank you, Uehara.
ありがとう上原君
You're so kind.
優しいね
But really, you don't have to.
あつでもいいよ いいってば
Score!
ゴール!
No, really! It's OK!
もうイヤ もういいよ
Hey, you!
(店員)あんた ずっと待ってるけど寒くないの?
Oh. I'm fine.
(菜緒)あっ大丈夫です
When I move around like this, I can stay warm.
こうやって体動かしてたほうが 体あったまるんですよ
OK. But don't catch a cold.
そう? 風邪ひかないようにね
Here you go. It's fresh cooked, and warm.
はいこれ できたてあったかいよ
Really? Are you sure?
えついいんですか?
Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます!
Is that Nao?
あれ吉川さん?
Yeah.
(上原)ああ
I guess you like girls that are a little weird.
上原ってちょっと 変わった子がタイプなんだな つに
Oh!
あつ
Uehara!
上原君
-Everybody's looking at you. -Really?
お前目立ちすぎ (菜緒)え?
I guess I went a little overboard.
やりすぎちゃつた
Jeez!
ったく つに
What?
何?
Well...
あついや
I was just glad that you came.
来てくれたんだなあって 思って
Yeah, well, my job ended pretty early.
まつバイト 結構早く終わったしな
I see. That's great.
そっか よかった
Thank you.
ありがとう
You totally look like a Daruma doll.
だるまだな完全に
-How can you say that? -Let's go.
(菜緒)何なの? 仩原)行くぞ
Really? But where?
(菜緒)え?行くってどこに?
If we don't hurry, we'll never be able to see all of these.
急がねえとこんなにたくさん 回りきらねーだろ
Yeah!
(菜緒) うん
What's wrong?
どうしたの?
Oh, it's nothing.
(上原)あっいや 何でもない
Where to first?
どっから行く?
I'm not so tactless as to interfere with you two.
あんたらの邪魔するほど 無粋じゃないんでね
Wow! Those two sure seem to be getting along well!
何かすっごい いい感じじゃない?
-I envy them. -Yeah.
(阿部)いいなあ (まりな) うん な) つ
Leave them be. Let's go!
(一星)ほっといてやれよ 行くぞ
-OK, fine. -OK.
(光石)は~い (まりな)は~い
What are you doing here?
(希)何やってんだ
Why are you here, Kitaura?
あれ北浦さん 何で何で?
-Are you on a trip too? -Yeah.
北浦さんも旅行? (希)ああ
-Are you alone? -Yes.
(阿部)お一人ですか?
Where are you going next?
(阿部) これからどちらへ
First to Ikaho shrine, then to Kajika bridge.
伊香保神社に行って そこから河鹿橋に かじかばし
That's exactly where I was going to go!
(阿部) 僕と全く一緒じゃないっすか!
Oh!
(菜緒)あつ
"It became known to help in achieving a successful romance."
"恋愛成就に 絶大な効果があり"
We've got to go here!
これ絶対行かなくちゃ
Right?
ねつ a
Hey!
(上原)おい
"However, you must be very careful if you already have a lover."
汝性) “ただし もう恋人のいる人は要注意,
"Since these two in the legend could not consummate their love,"
“仲の良すぎる男女には
"and putting a curse any couples that get along too well."
"災いをもたらすとの 話もある"
Do you want a sweet bun, Uehara?
(菜緒)あっ上原君 おまんじゅう食べる?
-A sweet bun? -Here.
はま (上原)まんじゅう? (菜趟はい
Where did you get that from?
(上愿どっから 出てきてんだよ
This lady gave it to me.
(菜趟さっき もらったんだ ご
I've been keeping it warm.
あつためといてあげた
-Thanks. -Sure.
菜上 緒原 はは いい (上愿はい (菜趟はい
-The filling is coming out. -Really?
あんが飛び出てんじゃねえかよ (菜緒)え?
Quit complaining! Here! Eat it!
文句言わないでよ ほれほれほれ
-I'll eat it myself. -No, you can't have it.
(上原)いい自分で食うよ (菜緒)あげないよ
-Give it here. -Give it back!
仩原)やだよ (菜緒)返して
I'll eat it.
私が食べる
-Hey! -Yum! That's good!
(菜緒)あっ 仩厕んっ!うまつ あん
Fine! I've got another one anyway.
(菜緒)いいもん もう1個持ってるから